<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on pop %eax</title>
    <link>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on pop %eax</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 21:22:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Bugs</title>
      <link>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/excellent-bugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 21:22:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/excellent-bugs/</guid>
      <description>Some bugs are interesting. Others are annoying. Some are fun. Some are just impossible. Many bugs are confusing. Others are are annoying. Some are just impossible. This is a list of those bugs: MRI disabled every iOS device in facility We can&amp;rsquo;t send mail more than 500 miles OpenOffice.org can&amp;rsquo;t print on Tuesday (see comment 28) I can&amp;rsquo;t log in when I stand up (and another similar story) A story about &amp;ldquo;magic&amp;rdquo; Print this file, your printer will jam gcj crashes in April and December, but only if you speak German in Austria Processor 5 doesn&amp;rsquo;t work if you&amp;rsquo;re standing too close A car that is allergic to vanilla ice cream Some employees change the monitor&amp;rsquo;s resolution without touching it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack to Wiki</title>
      <link>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/slack-to-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 13:20:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/slack-to-wiki/</guid>
      <description>One habbit I&amp;rsquo;ve started at work is called &amp;ldquo;slack to wiki&amp;rdquo;. Whenever I learn something new, or explain something to someone else, I try to document it on our internal wiki quickly and in a low effort way. If I come back to the topic again in the future I&amp;rsquo;ll modify the content and make it actully good.
This forms of a knowledge base which can grow, and also lets me reference past topics in future conversations more easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modulo and Remainder</title>
      <link>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/modulo-and-remainder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 17:56:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/modulo-and-remainder/</guid>
      <description>This is a quick test blog post to see if I could make mathjax and such work for me. It is not supposed to be complete right now.
Some Definitions  even a number is even there is no remainder when dividied by 2 equivalently $\{ 2k: k \in \mathbb{Z} \}$
 odd a number is odd if it is not even equivelently $\{ 2k+1: k \in \mathbb{Z} \}$
  This leads to the obvious question of what is a remainder?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Test</title>
      <link>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/first-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 17:46:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.brokenkernel.com/posts/first-test/</guid>
      <description>test test test</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>